stocks.exchange 2019-12-19

# Privacy policy

This cookie and privacy policy is for website [STEX](https://app.stex.com/en) (hereinafter “website”) and served by Etna Development OÜ (hereinafter “Company”, “we” or “us”) and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it (hereinafter ‘User’ or ‘you’). 

Company's activities are conducted in accordance with legislation of the Republic of Estonia and European Union law, and their provisions have to be taken into account. 

The Company encourage You to read this Cookie and Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services or transacting business with us. By using website, you are accepting the practices described in this Cookie and Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Cookie and Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us. 

##### Information We Collect About You

We are legally obliged to collect personal information that can identify you such as your name and email address and other information that identify you. When you provide personal information through our website, the information will be sent to our servers.

We may collect and store any personal information you enter on our website or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, birth data and telephone number, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). We also may request information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, other demographic information and other information like this;

We can keep all files you upload to our website, including images.

We may also periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from other sources like networks business partners, contractors and other third parties and add it to our account information or other information we have collected. Examples of information that we may receive include: updated delivery and address information, purchase history, and additional demographic information.

##### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record keeping purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time.

When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience.

Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our website, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our website.

We may allow our authorized service providers to serve cookies from our website to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our site, content and advertising.

You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. (Click "Help" in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly;

##### Other technologies

We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site. We also may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website visitors to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.

Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies, which are stored on the user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in email) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website.

##### How We Use the Information We Collect

We do the best according to the law and best practice in this area. We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * deliver the products and services that you have requested;
  * manage your account and provide you with customer support;
  * perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others; 
  * communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties; 
  * enforce our terms and conditions;
  * manage our business and perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. 

We may use financial information or payment method to protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, processing credit card payments, delivering packages, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our website. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes;

We also may disclose your information:

  * in response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; 
  * to defend against legal claims; 
  * when we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; 
  * to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; 
  * to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; 
  * to enforce our website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies; 
  * in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy; 
  * or as otherwise required by law. 

The user must take into account that, given the legal obligations of the company under the Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing Prevention Act and other relevant laws Company should keep personal information of the users, and such information cannot be removed or deleted by user’s request.

##### Your Choices About Collection and Use of Your Information

You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our website because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our website;

##### How We Protect Your Personal Information

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information. 

We want you to feel confident using our website to transact business. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending personal information through insecure email. 

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services.

##### Contacts

You can contact us by email [support@stex.com](mailto:support@stex.com)
